Gyuhyeon Hwang

Software Developer

Junior software developer specializing in server development. Use C++ and Python as primary languages. Familiar with collaboration and troubleshooting through the internship and team project experiences via Git and Slack. As a junior developer, I like to solve challenges and problems to improve myself. Also, would like to reach out to try various areas.

Contact

Email:

hwgyuhyeon@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/gyuhyeon/

Portfolio:

hgyuhyeon.github.io

Skill

- Python, C++
- Django, DRF
- MySQL, SQLite
- Linux
- Git, Slack, Notion

Education

Department of Computer Science – Chungbuk

National University

Bachelor of Science 2019.03 – 2024.02(Expected)

Computer Science – Angelo State University

Study Abroad 2022.01 – 2022.05

Languages

English – Intermediate

Korean - Native

Experience

Software Developer (Internship), 2022.06 – 2022.07

Headstart SV, Seoul, South Korea (Hybrid)

Worked as a Django/Python developer. Experience agile development with 7 team members. Manage and finalize the team project.

- Build and manage the server via AWS and docker.
- Implement web server API through Django.
- Test API & fix errors and problems.

Web Developer, 2021.06 – 2021.07

Flug Mediaworks, Cheongju, South Korea

Worked as a full-stack PHP/JavaScript developer. Implement web pages based on designed drafts and participate in maintenance.

- Implement a web page both front-end (HTML/CSS) and back-end (PHP/JavaScript).
- Translate the Korean web pages to English and implement an English version.
- Fix errors & problems of the web pages on service.

Project

Software Developer, 2022.06 – 2022.07

Recommade, Headstart SV internship program

- A website that recommends music according to the atmosphere of the photo.
- Design structure of the Django server and implement GET playlists and GET one playlist API under RESTful rules.
- Apply the AI model and React web project to the Django server.
- Connect Django, MySQL, Nginx, and React via docker-compose and deploy to AWS EC2.